<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_fastforward_description">Fast-forward</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_fullscreen_description">Full-screen mode</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_next_description">Next track</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_pause_description">Pause</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_play_description">Play</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_previous_description">Previous track</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_all_description">Repeat all</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_off_description">Repeat none</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_one_description">Repeat one</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_rewind_description">Rewind</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_shuffle_description">Shuffle</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_stop_description">Stop</string>
    <string name="exo_download_completed">Download completed</string>
    <string name="exo_download_description">Download</string>
    <string name="exo_download_downloading">Downloading</string>
    <string name="exo_download_failed">Download failed</string>
    <string name="exo_download_notification_channel_name">Downloads</string>
    <string name="exo_download_removing">Removing downloads</string>
    <string name="exo_item_list">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="exo_track_bitrate">%1$.2f Mbps</string>
    <string name="exo_track_mono">Mono</string>
    <string name="exo_track_resolution">%1$d × %2$d</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_none">None</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_text">Text</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_video">Video</string>
    <string name="exo_track_stereo">Stereo</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround">Surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround_5_point_1">5.1 surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround_7_point_1">7.1 surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="user_license_btn_text">User Agreement &amp; Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="user_license_new">"Important Notice&lt;br/> “Xiaomi Technology Co., Ltd.; Beijing Xiaomi Mobile Software Co., Ltd.” (hereinafter referred to as “Mi Home”) hereby reminds the user to carefully read and fully understand this “Software License and Service Agreement” (hereinafter referred to as “this Agreement”). Users should read carefully and fully understand the terms of this Agreement, in particular, the terms of the exemption or limitation of liability, dispute resolution, and applicable laws. The terms for exemption or limitation of liability will be in bold type, and you will need to read them carefully. Please read attentively and choose whether to accept or not accept this Agreement (minors should be accompanied by their legal guardian while they read). Your downloads, installation, use of the software, and access to account will be deemed acceptance of this Agreement and will be subject to the terms of this Agreement. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Mi Home reserves the right to amend this Agreement, the updated terms of the Agreement to be posted on the official website or software, effective from the date of their promulgation. Users can re-download and install the software or website to view the latest version of the terms of this Agreement. After Mi Home modifies the terms of this Agreement, if the user does not accept the revised terms, they should please stop using Mi Home software and services provided by Mi Home; users who continue to use Mi Home software and services provided by Mi Home shall be deemed to have accepted the revised Agreement. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 1. General Provisions&lt;br/> 1.1. This Agreement is between you (hereinafter also referred to as User) and Mi Home and its operational affiliates (Affiliates) for downloading, installing and using Mi Home’s “Mi Home” software (this Software), including the agreement entered into for the use of Mi Home’s related services. &lt;br/> 1.2. This Software and these services provided by Mi Home include but are not limited to software and services installed on mobile smart terminal devices, for the use of smart terminal users to provide official drivers and Mi Home services. &lt;br/> 1.3. The ownership rights and operational rights for this Software and these services are owned by Mi Home. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 2. Scope of Software Licensing&lt;br/> 2.1. Mi Home gives the User a personal, non-transferable, non-sublicensable and non-exclusive license in respect of this Software. &lt;br/> 2.2. The User may install, use, display, and run the Software on a single mobile terminal device for non-commercial purposes. However, the User may not install, use or run this Software for the purpose of commercial operations, and may not copy, change, modify, mount, or create any derivative works from the Software or any data released into the memory of any terminal device during the operation of the Software and the interactive data between the Client and Server, including in the form of but not limited to the use of plug-ins, add-ons, or unauthorized third-party tools/services to access the Software and related systems. If you need to sell, copy, or distribute the Software commercially, as for example pre-installed and bundled software, you must obtain written authorization and license from Mi Home. &lt;br/> 2.3. The User shall not install the Software on terminal devices that are not expressly authorized by Mi Home, including but not limited to set-top boxes, game consoles, TV sets and DVD players, without the permission of Mi Home. &lt;br/> 2.4. The User may make a copy of the Software for their own use of the Software and services solely for backup purposes. The backup copy must contain all the copyright information contained in the original Software. &lt;br/> 2.5. Except as expressly authorized in this Agreement, Mi Home shall not give any other rights to the User, and if the User makes use of any other rights they shall separately obtain written consent from Mi Home. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 3. Software Acquisition, Installation, and Upgrading&lt;br/> 3.1. The User should download and install this Software product according to the website or method designated by Mi Home. Beware downloading this Software from non-designated websites to prevent mobile devices from being infected by malicious programs that can destroy user data and obtain user privacy information. If the User obtains the Software or an installation program with the same name as the Software from a third party who is not authorized by Mi Home, Mi Home cannot guarantee the normal use of the Software and will not be responsible for any losses caused thereby. &lt;br/> 3.2. The User must select the software version that matches the terminal device on which it is to be installed. Otherwise, any software problems, equipment problems, or damages caused by the mismatch between the Software and equipment model shall be borne by the User. &lt;br/> 3.3. In order to improve the user experience and improve the contents of their service, Mi Home reserves the right to replace, modify and upgrade the Software from time to time, and also reserves the right to charge a fee for the said replacement, modification, or upgrade, but will get your consent in advance. The default for this Software is to activate the Upgrade Notification function; depending on the differences between the User’s software version, Mi Home provides the User with the opening of activating this feature. After a new version of this Software is released, Mi Home does not guarantee that the old version will continue to be available. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 4. Standards of Use&lt;br/> 4.1. The User may use this Software and these services in compliance with the law and this Agreement. The User shall not carry out the following acts: &lt;br/> 4.1.1. Removing copyright information from this Software and its copies, and modifying, deleting, or avoiding technical measures put in place for the protection of intellectual property rights; &lt;br/> 4.1.2. Reverse engineering the Software, such as disassembling, decompiling, or otherwise attempting to obtain the source code of the Software; &lt;br/> 4.1.3. Adding to, subtracting from, or changing the function or operating results of the Software by modifying or forging software operational commands or data, or operating or disseminating the Software to the public to be utilized for the aforementioned purposes, whether or not these actions are for commercial purposes; &lt;br/> 4.1.4. Using the Software for any actions that endanger cybersecurity, including but not limited to the use of unauthorized data or access to unauthorized servers/accounts; unauthorized access to a public network or other operating systems and deleting, modifying, or adding to the stored information; unauthorized attempts to detect, scan, or test the software system or network vulnerabilities, or other acts to undermine network security; attempt to interfere with or damage the normal operation of the software system or website, or deliberately spread malicious programs or viruses. as well as other acts that disrupt normal network information services; and fake or partial TCP/IP packet names; &lt;br/> 4.1.5. Registering or using the Software and services using third-party compatible software not developed, authorized, or endorsed by Mi Home, or make, publish and distribute such tools; &lt;br/> 4.1.6. Unauthorized implementation of the Software and the information contained therein without the written consent of Mi Home, including but not limited to the following acts: using, renting, lending, copying, modifying, linking, reprinting, compiling, issuing, publishing, establishing a mirror site, or making unauthorized use of the Software to develop related derivative products, works, services, plug-ins, add-ons, that are compatible, interconnected, etc.; &lt;br/> 4.1.7. Using the Software to post, transmit, broadcast, or store content that is in violation of national laws, that endangers national security, the national unity of China, social stability, and public order, or any content that is inappropriate, insulting, libelous, obscene, violent, or in violation of national laws, regulations, and policies; &lt;br/> 4.1.8. Using the Software to publish, transmit, broadcast, or store content that infringes the legal rights for others' intellectual property and trade secrets; &lt;br/> 4.1.9. Publishing, transmitting, and disseminating advertisements and junk information in batches by using this Software; &lt;br/> 4.1.10. Making other use of the Software and services provided by Mi Home in some unlawful fashion or for any unlawful purpose, or that is in some other way inconsistent with the use permitted by this Agreement. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 4.2. Information Release Standards&lt;br/> 4.2.1. You may use this Software to post information, views, data, text, information, usernames, pictures, photos, personal information, audio, video files, links and other information that is your original creation or you are entitled to publish. You must guarantee that you own the intellectual property for your uploaded content or that you have been legally authorized to do so and that your use of the Software and services does not infringe upon the legal rights of any third party. &lt;br/> 4.2.2. Your use of this Software is subject to the seven bottom lines of Chinese laws and regulations, which include the socialist system, the national interests, the legitimate rights and interests of citizens, public order, ethics, and the authenticity of information. &lt;br/> 4.2.3. You may not use this Software in the following acts, including but not limited to: &lt;br/> 4.2.3.1. Making, copying, publishing, disseminating, or storing contents in violation of national laws and regulations, including: &lt;br/> (1) Opposing the basic principles set forth in the Constitution of China; &lt;br/> (2) Endangering national security, disclosing state secrets, subverting state power and undermining state unity; &lt;br/> (3) Damaging the honor and interests of the state; &lt;br/> (4) Instigating ethnic hatred or ethnic discrimination, and undermining national unity; &lt;br/> (5) Undermining the country's religious policies and promoting cults and feudal superstitions; &lt;br/> (6) Spreading rumors, disrupting social order, and undermining social stability; &lt;br/> (7) Promoting obscenity, pornography, gambling, violence, homicide, terrorism, or abetting crimes; &lt;br/> (8) Insulting or slandering others and infringing upon the legitimate rights and interests of others; &lt;br/> (9) Inciting illegal assemblies, associations, marches, or demonstrations, and gathering crowds to disturb social order; &lt;br/> (10) Representing illegal civil organization activities; &lt;br/> (11) Containing other contents prohibited by laws and administrative regulations; &lt;br/> 4.2.3.2. Publishing, transmitting, disseminating, and storing content that infringes on the legitimate rights of other people's reputation, portraiture rights, intellectual property rights, and trade secrets; &lt;br/> 4.2.3.3. Fabricating facts and concealing the truth in order to mislead or deceive others; &lt;br/> 4.2.3.4. Publishing, transmitting, and disseminating advertisements and spam; &lt;br/> 4.2.3.5. Engaging in other acts that violate laws, regulations, policies, public order and moral integrity, and social ethics. &lt;br/> 4.2.4. You may not carry out any commercial activities such as advertising or selling goods using this Software without Mi Home’s permission. &lt;br/> 4.3 You understand and agree that: &lt;br/> 4.3.1. Mi Home will determine whether the User is suspected of violating the above-mentioned usage regulations and terminate the use of their license or take other restrictive measures that may be taken according to the Agreement; &lt;br/> 4.3.2. Mi Home will directly delete information that allegedly infringes or is suspected of infringing upon the legal rights of others or being in violation of this Agreement in the use of this Software; &lt;br/> 4.3.3. The User shall bear legal liability in their own name for any damage to a third party caused by the User's violation of the aforementioned usage regulations, and shall ensure that Mi Home will be exempt from any loss or expense; &lt;br/> 4.3.4. If the User’s violation of the provisions of the relevant laws or agreements results in Mi Home suffering losses, third-party claims, or fees levied by the administrative authorities, the User shall make compensation for resulting losses and/or expenses incurred by Mi Home, including reasonable legal fees and the costs of investigation and evidence collection. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 5. Privacy Policy and Personal Information Protection&lt;br/> 5.1. Protecting your personal information is important to Mi Home. In order to provide software functionality and improve user experience, Mi Home will collect data as follows. &lt;br/> 5.1.1. We may collect any or all of the personal information you provide to us, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, Mi Account information (such as your security-related information, name, birthday, and gender), information or data that your access to the Mi Home platform synchronizes, the account and related settings created on the Mi Home platform, the device you added or messages you sent, feedback, and any other information you provide to us. &lt;br/> 5.1.2. Information related to your handheld terminal or SIM card: Information related to running the Mi Home handheld terminal, for example, the IMEI number, IMSI number, system version, device manufacturer information, model name, and network operator. &lt;br/> 5.1.3. Device information: Device information associated with your account, for example, MAC address, DID, and information collected by the corresponding device sensors (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, action/screen detection, body temperature, body weight, and on/off status), as well as the operating conditions of device consumables (such as the filter and filter service life). &lt;br/> 5.1.4. Information we specify about you: We may collect and use information such as your Mi Account. &lt;br/> 5.1.5. Location information (specific services/features only): Various types of information related to your location, for example, country code, city code, mobile network code, cell ID, latitude and longitude information, and language settings. &lt;br/> 5.1.6. Login information: Information related to your use of certain features and devices. Examples include cookies and other anonymous identifier technologies, IP addresses, temporary message history, and standard system logs. &lt;br/> 5.1.7. Other information: Device-bound accounts (e-mail and phone number), connected Wi-Fi account and password, geo-location information, etc. &lt;br/> We may also collect other types of anonymous information that are not associated with individuals. For example, it is possible to collect the device model and firmware version number of the device used to access Mi Home when using a particular service. The purpose of collecting such information is to improve the services we provide you with. The type and amount of information collected depends on how you use, join, or participate in our products and/or services. &lt;br/> 5.2. Mi Home will collect, use and protect your data in accordance with Mi Home’s Privacy Policy. You can view Mi Home’s Privacy Policy in the Mi Home app. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 6. Service Risk and Exemption Disclaimer&lt;br/> 6.1. The User must have their own mobile terminal device to go online and the equipment necessary to use telecommunication value-added services, and is responsible for paying the costs for their personal mobile terminal device to go online, or any third-party communication fees, information fees, or other related costs (including but not limited to those of telecommunication or mobile communication providers). In the case of telecommunication value-added services, we recommend that you confirm the associated costs with your telecommunication value-added service provider. &lt;br/> 6.2. Mi Home and its Affiliates shall not be responsible for any losses suffered by the User due to third-party failures such as communication line malfunctions, technical problems, network or mobile terminal equipment failure, system instability and other causes of force majeure. &lt;br/> 6.3. Like most internet software, this Software may be affected by various security issues such as but not limited to human error, network service quality, and the social environment. For example, others may make use of the User’s information to carry out real-life harassment; if the User downloads and installs other software or visits other sites containing Trojans or other viruses, they may threaten the User's terminal device information and data security, thereby affecting the normal use of the software, and so on. Users should strengthen the protection of their information security and information awareness, and pay attention to strengthening their password protection in order to avoid loss and harassment. &lt;br/> 6.4. As a result of the User using this Software, or when they request specific services provided by Mi Home, this Software may call upon third-party systems or third-party software to support the User's use or access; the results of such use or access being provided by the third party, Mi Home does not guarantee the security, accuracy, validity, or other uncertainties of results achieved through third-party systems or third-party software support, and Mi Home will not be held liable for any disputes or damages so arising. &lt;br/> 6.5. Mi Home reminds the User that, in order to protect the company's autonomy to develop and adjust its business, it has the right to modify or discontinue service at any time without notice to the User. Mi Home’s right to modify or discontinue service is not dependent upon the User or any third party. &lt;br/> 6.6. Except as expressly provided for by law and regulation, we will do our utmost to ensure that the Software as well as the technology and information involved in it is safe, efficient, accurate and reliable subject to the limitations of existing technology. &lt;br/> 6.7. Any of the following circumstances caused by or in connection with personal injury or incidental, indirect financial damages due to the User, including but not limited to, lost profits, lost data, business interruption, or other business damages or losses, shall be borne by the User: (1) the use or failure to use licensed Software; (2) the unauthorized use of the Software by a third party or the alteration of the User's data; (3) the costs and damages incurred by the User in the use of the Software; 4) the User's misunderstanding of the Software; and (5) other Software-related losses not caused by Mi Home. &lt;br/> 6.8. All wrongdoers shall bear all responsibility according to the law for any physical or financial harm or loss caused or likely to be caused by misleading or deceptive behavior between the User and other users of the Software by means of it. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 7. Intellectual Property Disclaimer&lt;br/> 7.1 Mi Home is the owner of the intellectual property rights for this Software. All copyrights, trademarks, patents, trade secrets and other intellectual property rights of the Software, as well as all information content (including but not limited to text, pictures, audio, video, graphics, interface design, layout framework, related data, and electronic documents) are protected by the laws and regulations of the People's Republic of China and the corresponding international treaties; Mi Home enjoys the aforementioned intellectual property rights. &lt;br/> 7.2 Without the written consent of Mi Home, the User shall not exercise or use any intellectual property rights for any commercial or non-commercial purposes for themselves or any third party. Mi Home reserves the right to pursue legal liabilities for the aforementioned acts. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 8. Agreement Changes&lt;br/> 8.1 Mi Home reserves the right to modify the terms of this Agreement if necessary. Once there is a change in the terms of the Agreement, the amended terms of the Agreement will be announced on the relevant pages. If the User does not agree with the changes, they should take the initiative to cancel this service. If the User continues to use the service, they are deemed to have accepted the change to the terms of this Agreement. &lt;br/> 8.2. Mi Home and its Affiliates have the right to modify or change the fee-based services they provide, fees, payment methods, service fees and terms of service. At the time of providing service Mi Home may start to charge some service Users now or in the future. If the User refuses to pay such fees, the related service cannot be continued after the charge starts. Mi Home and its Affiliates will make their best efforts to notify the User of such modifications or changes by email or other means. &lt;br/> 9. Applicable Laws and Dispute Resolution&lt;br/> 9.1. The validity and interpretation of the terms of this Agreement shall apply the mainland regional laws of the People's Republic of China. In the absence of relevant law, reference is made to the use of international commercial practices and/or commercial practices. &lt;br/> 9.2. The place of signing for this Agreement is Haidian District, Beijing. &lt;br/> 9.3. The User and Mi Home unanimously agree that any dispute arising out of this service shall be settled by negotiation between both parties, and failing agreement either party may bring litigation to the court with jurisdiction over this Agreement’s place of signing for resolution. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 10. Other&lt;br/> 10.1. Users may have separate agreements, relevant business rules and the like (hereinafter referred to as Individual Agreements) when using this Software for a particular service. Please read and agree to the relevant Separate Agreement before using such a service. &lt;br/> 10.2. The effective date of this Agreement is the 20th of October, 2017. &lt;br/> 10.3. The titles of all terms of this Agreement are for the convenience of reading only and have no actual meaning in themselves, nor can they be used as the basis for an interpretation of the meaning of this Agreement. &lt;br/> 10.4. If the terms of this Agreement are partly invalid or unenforceable for whatever reason, the remaining provisions are still valid and binding on both parties. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Mi Home&lt;br/>&lt;br/>"</string>
    <string name="user_license_title">Mi Home User Agreement &amp; Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="user_privacy_new">"Our rivacy policy was updated on the 20th of October, 2017. We have revised our Privacy Policy, and from this date onwards this policy can provide details about how we manage the personal information you disclose when using any Mi Home products or services, with the exception of certain Mi Home products or services that provide their own independent Privacy Policy.&lt;br/> Please take some time to become familiar with our privacy practices, and please let us know if you have any questions. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Our promise to you&lt;br/> This Privacy Policy sets out how Xiaomi and its affiliates (hereafter Xiaomi or We) collect, use, disclose, process and protect the information you provide through the Mi Home app when using our products and services. If we ask you to provide certain information to verify your identity when using Mi Home products and services, we will use this information strictly in accordance with this policy and/or our user terms and conditions. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> This policy is formulated with your needs in mind; it is important that you fully understand our personal data collection and usage practices and that you are ultimately in control of the personal information you provide. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> In this Privacy Policy, personal information refers to the information itself or other information accessible to Xiaomi that allows us to identify the data of specific individuals. Such personal information includes your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> By using Mi Home products and services, you acknowledge that you have read, acknowledged, and accepted all the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy, including any changes we may make at any time. We are committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality and security of your personal information in accordance with applicable laws (including the data protection laws specific to your location). At the same time we promise our staff and agents will fulfill these obligations. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Finally, what we want is the best experience for our users. If you have any questions about the data processing practices outlined in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at privacy@xiaomi.com so that we can handle your special needs. We are happy to deal with your problem directly. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> What information is collected and how is it used? &lt;br/>&lt;br/> The types of information collected&lt;br/> We will ask you to provide the personal information necessary to provide you with our services. If you do not provide this personal information, we may not be able to provide you with our products or services. &lt;br/> We collect the following types of information (whether or not they are personal information): &lt;br/> • Information you provide or upload to us: We may collect any or all of the personal information you provide to us, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, Mi Account information (such as your security-related information, name, birthday, or gender), information or data that your access to the Mi Home platform synchronizes, the account and related settings created on the Mi Home platform, the device you added or messages you sent, feedback, and any other information you provide to us. &lt;br/> • Information related to your handheld terminal or SIM card: Information related to running the Mi Home handheld terminal. For example, the IMEI number, IMSI number, system version, device manufacturer information, model name, and network operator. &lt;br/> • Device information: Device information associated with your account. For example, MAC address, DID, and information collected by the corresponding device sensors (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, action/screen detection, body temperature, body weight, and on/off status), as well as the operating conditions of device consumables (such as the filter, filter service life, etc.). &lt;br/> • Information we specify about you: We may collect and use information such as your Mi Account. &lt;br/> • Location information (specific services/features only): Various types of information related to your location. For example, country code, city code, mobile network code, cell ID, latitude and longitude information, and language settings. &lt;br/> • Login information: Information related to your use of certain features and devices. Examples include cookies and other anonymous identifier technologies, IP addresses, temporary message history, and standard system logs. &lt;br/> • Additional information: Environmental characteristic value or ECV (device-bound account (e-mail and phone number), connected Wi-Fi account and password, geo-location information, etc.) &lt;br/>&lt;br/> We may also collect other types of anonymous information that are not associated with individuals. For example, it is possible to collect the device model and firmware version number of the device used to access Mi Home when using a particular service. The purpose of collecting such information is to improve the services we provide you. The type and amount of information collected depends on how you use, join, or participate in our products and/or services. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> How this personal information will be used&lt;br/> The purpose of collecting personal information is to provide you with products and/or services and to ensure that we comply with applicable laws. You hereby agree that we process personal information for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy and disclose personal information to our affiliates (which cover communications, social media, technology and cloud businesses) and third-party service providers (as defined below). &lt;br/> We may use your personal information for the following purposes: &lt;br/> • Providing, processing, maintaining, improving, and developing the products and/or services we provide to you, as well as through devices or Mi Home-provided services. &lt;br/> • Communicating with you about your devices, services, or any general inquiries such as updates, device firmware/software upgrades, customer advisory support, related information, notifications, and more. &lt;br/> • Analyzing and developing statistical information related to the use of our products and services to better improve them. &lt;br/> • Store and maintain information about you for our business operations or legal obligations. &lt;br/> Here's more details on how we use your information, which may include personal information. &lt;br/> • Creating your account. The personal information collected when creating an account on a mobile device is used to create a user's personal account and profile page. &lt;br/> • Providing location-based services. We may use location information to provide you with the best possible user experience when using Mi Home and accessing Mi Home devices, such as analyzing and providing information about the surrounding weather, air quality, water quality, and launching the appropriate devices and experiences in advance according to your choices. You can turn this feature off at any time by entering device settings or stopping your use of this application. access. &lt;br/> • Device access. In order to access Mi Home, your device must connect to the network. Therefore, when adding devices to the Mi Home app, you need to enter the corresponding Wi-Fi name and password. This information is only used for the device distribution network. We will encrypt the Wi-Fi and password data you input and store it in your mobile terminal; we will not upload it to the server, you can enter the device to delete the information at any time. &lt;br/> • Device status display. Status information (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, action/screen detection, body temperature, body weight, and on/off status), as well as the operating conditions of device consumables (such as the filter, filter service life, etc.) allow you to remotely view the status of your device so you can see how well it is running in your home at any time. &lt;br/> • Setting up automated tasks. Event information reported by your device (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, and action/screen detection) can be used to create your own personal automated tasks, such as accessing Mi Home’s temperature sensor when the temperature is higher than 30℃ to access control of Mi Home’s smart air conditioner to start cooling. &lt;br/> • Providing push services. The account and IMEI number will also be used to provide Mi Home push services to send notifications to users. You can turn this feature off at any time by changing your preferences under Message Settings. &lt;br/> • Verifying user identity. Mi Home uses ECV values to verify user identities and ensure that hackers or unauthorized persons cannot log in. &lt;br/> • Collecting user feedback. The feedback you choose to provide is extremely valuable to helping Mi Home improve our services. In order to follow the feedback you choose to provide, Mi Home may use the personal information you provide to contact you and to keep records. &lt;br/> • Sending notifications. From time to time we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as unexpected device health notifications, customized device push notifications (such as motion detection alerts, cleanups, etc.), or changes to our terms and conditions or policies. &lt;br/> • Direct marketing. We may use your name, phone number, email address, Mi and Mi Home accounts, and IMEI numbers to provide you with promotional materials for products and services from Xiaomi and our partners (providing web, mobile applications, and cloud products and services). To provide a better user experience, we recommend these products, services, and events based on your purchase history, site browsing history, birthday, age, gender, and location. We strictly adhere to the data protection laws of your location and require independent, express permission, so we will only use your personal information with your consent or your lack of objection. You have the right to terminate our use of personal data intended for direct marketing. If you no longer wish to receive certain categories of e-mail, you can unsubscribe using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each e-mail. We will not send your personal information to our business partners for direct marketing. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> With whom do we share your information? &lt;br/> We will not sell your personal information to a third party. &lt;br/> From time to time, we may disclose your personal information to third parties (as defined below) to provide the products or services you request. We may disclose information to third-party service providers and affiliates listed below in this section. In the circumstances described in this section, you can rest assured that Xiaomi will only share your personal information based on your authorization. You understand that Xiaomi will comply with applicable local data protection laws through contractual third-party practices and obligations when Xiaomi shares your personal information with third-party service providers under any of the circumstances described below. Xiaomi will contract to ensure that third-party service providers comply with the privacy standards applicable to them in your jurisdiction. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Sharing information within our group and with third party service providers&lt;br/> In order to successfully conduct business and provide you with the full functionality of our products and services, we may from time to time disclose your personal information to other Xiaomi affiliates (dealing with communications, social media, technology or cloud businesses) or our third party service providers (our mailing houses, delivery service providers, telecommunications companies, data centers, data storage facilities, customer service providers, advertising and promotion service providers, and agents representing Xiaomi) [Affiliates and/or other third parties] (collectively third party service providers). Such third party service providers may handle your personal information on behalf of Xiaomi or for one or more of the above items. When using certain mobile applications on our devices, we may share your IP address with third parties in order to provide you with certain services you request. If you no longer wish to allow us to share this information, please contact us at privacy@xiaomi.com. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Sharing information with the Xiaomi Ecosystem Company&lt;br/> Xiaomi works together with a group of other cool companies to form the Mi Ecosystem. A Mi Ecosystem company is an independent entity invested and operated by Xiaomi and is an expert in these fields. Xiaomi may disclose your personal information to a Mi Ecosystem company in order to provide and improve exciting products and services (including software and hardware) from the Mi Ecosystem. Some products and services still use the Xiaomi/Mi Home brands, but others may use their own brands. From time to time, the Mi Ecosystem may share data related to Xiaomi/Mi Home brand products and services in order to provide software and hardware services for better functionality and user experience. If Xiaomi is involved in the acquisition, merger, acquisition or disposal of all or any part of its assets, we will notify by email and/or prominently on our website of any changes to the ownership of your personal information or its use, as well as any options you may have regarding your personal information. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Sharing information with others&lt;br/> Mi Home may disclose your personal information without further consent, as required by applicable law. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Information that does not require consent&lt;br/> • We may share anonymous information with third parties (such as advertisers on our website) in an aggregated form for commercial purposes; we may share general usage trends for our services, such as the number of customers in certain groups who buy certain products or engage in certain transactions. &lt;br/> • In order to avoid doubt, Xiaomi may collect, use or disclose your personal information, without your consent, in the circumstances and to the extent expressly permitted by the Law on Local Data Protection (for example, in order to comply with a summons), and we may disclose your information without your consent, in good faith, for the purposes of protecting our rights, protecting your safety or the safety of others, and disclosing for investigation of fraud or responding to governmental requests. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Security&lt;br/> Xiaomi’s security measures&lt;br/> We promise to keep your personal information safe. To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or other similar risks, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and management processes to protect the information we collect from your mobile device. We will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> For example, when you visit your Mi Account, you can choose our two-step verification process to ensure better security. When you send or receive information from Mi Home devices to our servers, we ensure that they are encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and other algorithms. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> All of your personal information is stored on secure servers and protected in controlled facilities. We classify your data by importance and sensitivity and ensure that your personal information has the highest level of security. We guarantee that employees and third-party service providers who provide your products and services to you by accessing this information will have strict contractual confidentiality obligations and will be subject to disciplinary action or termination of cooperation if they fail to meet these obligations. In addition, we have specialized access controls for cloud-based data storage. All in all, we regularly review the practice of collecting, storing and processing information, including physical security measures to prevent any unauthorized access and use. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> We will take all practicable steps to protect your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the internet is not always safe and therefore we cannot guarantee the security or completeness of any personal information as it travels bidirectionally over the Internet. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> What you can do: &lt;br/> • You can help protect the security of your personal information by not disclosing your login password or account information to anyone (unless they have been duly authorized by you). Whenever you log into Mi Home as the user of your Mi Account, you should always log out when the session ends, especially when you log in on someone else's computer or a public Internet terminal. &lt;br/> • Xiaomi cannot be responsible for any security breach caused by third parties accessing your personal information due to your inability to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Notwithstanding the above, you must notify us immediately in the event of the unauthorized use of your account by any other user of the internet, or any other security breach. &lt;br/> • Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your personal information. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Retention policies&lt;br/> We will retain your personal information for the purpose of collecting information if necessary, or to comply with applicable legal requirements or allowances. We will not retain personal information as long as we reasonably conclude that the retention of personal information does not achieve the purpose of collecting personal information and that we no longer need to retain said information for legal purposes, dispute resolution, the enforcement of our agreement, or other commercial purposes, or we will eliminate ways to associate the personal information with specific individuals. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Access other features on your device&lt;br/> Our applications may have access to certain features on your device, such as enabling e-mail contacts, SMS storage, Wi-Fi network status, and more. This information is used to allow these applications to run on your device and to allow you to interact with them. At any time, you may revoke their license by closing the application at the device level or by contacting us at privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/>&lt;br/> You can control your information! &lt;br/> Control settings&lt;br/> Xiaomi acknowledges that everyone's privacy concerns may vary. As a result, we provide some examples of the various ways Xiaomi offers you to choose from to limit the collection, use, disclosure, or processing of your personal information and to control your privacy settings: &lt;br/> • Turn user experience planning and location access on or off; &lt;br/> • Log into or out of your Mi Account; &lt;br/> If you have previously granted us permission to use your personal information for the aforementioned reasons, you may change your decision at any time by contacting us in writing or by sending an e-mail to privacy@xiaomi.com. &lt;br/> • You have the right to request access to and/or correction of any personal information we hold about you. When you update your personal information, you will be asked to verify your identity before we process your request. As soon as we have sufficient information to process your request to access or correct your personal information, we will respond to your request as long as applicable under the Data Protection Act. &lt;br/> • We usually provide these services for free, but we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for data access requests. &lt;br/> • If you would like to request access to personal data held by us or if you believe any information we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or e-mail us at the e-mail address provided. E-mail: privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/> • For more details regarding the personal information in your Mi Home account, you can log into your account to access and change this information. &lt;br/> Revoking consent&lt;br/> • You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use, and/or disclosure of personal information held or controlled by us by sending an e-mail to privacy@xiaomi.com. We will process your request within a reasonable time after you have made your request and will not, at your request, collect, use, and/or disclose your personal information thereafter&lt;br/> • Please note that the revocation of you consent may result in legal consequences. We will process the scope of your personal information which may, depending on your revocation, indicate that you cannot enjoy Mi Home products and services. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Transferring personal information outside the jurisdiction to which you belong&lt;br/> If we need to transfer personal information outside your jurisdiction, whether it be to an affiliate (dealing with communications, social media, technology, or cloud services) or to a third-party service provider, we will apply all applicable laws. In particular, we will ensure that all such transfers meet the requirements of applicable local data protection laws by implementing the appropriate safeguards. Xiaomi may process or back up your personal information using overseas facilities operated and controlled by Mi Home. Currently, Xiaomi has data centers in Beijing, the United States, Singapore, and Germany. These overseas jurisdictions may or may not have data protection laws that are similar to the data protection laws of your jurisdiction. While we may transfer and store your personal information to our overseas facilities, this does not change our commitment to protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Other Provisions&lt;br/> Minors&lt;br/> • We consider it a parental responsibility to monitor children's use of our products and services. However, our policy does not require obtaining minors' personal information or sending any promotional materials to such groups. &lt;br/> • Xiaomi will not seek or attempt to seek to receive any personal information from minors. If a parent or guardian has reason to believe that minors submitted personal information to Mi Home without their prior consent, please contact us to ensure that such personal information is deleted and that any minor’s subscription to an applicable Mi Home service is cancelled. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Priority&lt;br/> If you agree to the applicable user agreement and there is an inconsistency between said user agreement and this Privacy Policy, the user agreement will prevail. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Applicable laws&lt;br/> [This Privacy Policy is governed by the law of Singapore.] We do not represent or guarantee that this Privacy Policy complies with the privacy laws of any jurisdiction and therefore you should not interpret the Privacy Policy in accordance with these laws. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Privacy Policy updates&lt;br/> We conduct regular reviews of our privacy practices and we may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by e-mail (at the e-mail address specified in your account) or by posting on the Mi Home app or via mobile devices so that you can understand the information we collect and how we use them information. Such changes to the Privacy Policy will apply from the effective date provided by the notice or on the website. We encourage you to check this page regularly for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of our products and our services provided via the website, phone, and/or any other device will be deemed to be an updated Privacy Policy. We will obtain your consent again when we collect more personal information from you or if we wish to use or disclose your personal information for new purposes. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Do I have to agree to any third-party terms and conditions? &lt;br/> Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products and services provided by third parties. Mi Home products and services may include third-party products and services, as well as links to third-party websites. Your information may also be collected when you use these products or services. Therefore, we strongly recommend that you take the time to read these third-party privacy policies just as you would read ours. We are not responsible for how third parties use the personal information they collect from you, nor do we control their use. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites linked through our services. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> When you use these specific products, the following third-party terms and privacy policies apply: &lt;br/>&lt;br/> • When using the Google input method you must agree to the Google terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://www.google.com/policies/privacy>http://www.google.com/policies/privacy&lt;/a>&lt;br/> • When using the SwiftKey input method you must agree to the SwiftKey terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://swiftkey.com/en/privacy>http://swiftkey.com/en/privacy&lt;/a>&lt;br/> • When using the Fleksy input method you must agree to the Fleksy terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://feedback.fleksy.com/tos>http://feedback.fleksy.com/tos&lt;/a>&lt;br/>&lt;br/> Social media (features) and widgets&lt;br/> Our website includes some social media features, including Facebook Like buttons, as well as widgets such as the Share button. These features may collect your IP address and the pages you visit on our website, and may set cookies for the proper functioning of the feature. Social media features and widgets may be hosted by third parties or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are subject to the Privacy Policy of the companies providing them. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Single sign-in&lt;br/> Depending on the jurisdiction to which you belong, you may be able to log into our website using the login service provided by Facebook Connect or Open ID. These services will verify your identity and allow you to choose whether to share certain personal information with us, such as your name and e-mail address, to pre-populate our registration form. Services such as Facebook Connect allow you to choose whether or not to post your personal information on this site on your profile page to share with others online. &lt;br/>&lt;br/> Contact us&lt;br/> If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or if you have any questions about the collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information by Xiaomi, please contact our Data Protection Officer at the address below and mention Privacy Policy:&lt;br/>&lt;br/> Xiaomi Singapore Pte Ltd&lt;br/> #02-12, 20 Cross Street, China Square Central&lt;br/> Singapore 048422&lt;br/> E-mail: privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/>&lt;br/> Thank you for taking the time to familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy! &lt;br/>&lt;br/>"</string>
</resources>
